<products>
<item id="1">
<title>Zombie Family Car Stickers</title>
<url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B0074JC5VW/?tag=047-20</url>
<description>
<price>$10.28</price>
<brief>Show off your ever growing family with these shambling zombie family car stickers.</brief>
<long>Show off your ever growing family with these shambling zombie family car stickers. Put them on your minivan and display your love for zombies and wholesale family things – or infect random vehicles with these stickers and proclaim them to be apart of your zombie army!</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="2">
<title>Qlocktwo Designer Clock</title>
<url>http://store.biegertfunk.com/us/</url>
<description>
<price>$599.99</price>
<brief>The qlocktwo is an uber expensive digital clock that is available in many different colors, and has a very unique way of displaying the time.</brief>
<long>The qlocktwo is an uber expensive digital clock that is available in many different colors, and has a very unique way of displaying the time. This designer clock is a great gift for someone who has it all, and also makes a great house warming gift.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="3">
<title>Radio Control Mario Kart</title>
<url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B005B8LPO6/?tag=047-20</url>
<description>
<price>$99.99</price>
<brief>Control a real life Mario Kart and tear up the streets with this radio controlled blue shell launching, star grabbing, banana dropping, mushroom abusing Mario Kart.</brief>
<long>Control a real life Mario Kart and tear up the streets with this radio controlled blue shell launching, star grabbing, banana dropping, mushroom abusing Mario Kart. This Mario Kart is a battery powered and has a max speed of 10 mph, and makes a great gift for kids.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="4">
<title>Das Boot Beer Mug</title>
<url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B001LXUKFA/?tag=047-20</url>
<description>
<price>$24.99</price>
<brief>Celebrate Oktoberfest like a real German by drinking from DAS BOOT!</brief>
<long>Celebrate Oktoberfest like a real German by drinking from DAS BOOT! This massive shoe holds 67 ounces, or roughly five beers in a single glass – enough to get you singing songs from the old country that you’re probably not even from.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="5">
<title>Pillow Fight Weapons</title>
<url>http://www.bryanku.com/Pillow-Fight</url>
<description>
<price>Concept</price>
<brief>Pillow weapons are the best excuse for a pillow fight!</brief>
<long>Pillow fights aren't a kid's game anymore - pick up your battle axe and get ready for things to get ugly - the pillow wars have begun! These shaped pillows include a scimitar, grenade, nunchucks, ninja star, battle axe, and even a light saber pillow weapon!</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="6">
<title>Shot Glass Roulette</title>
<url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B003VZYQWY/?tag=047-20</url>
<description>
<price>$15.99</price>
<brief>If somehow you are still sober after playing a couple of games of shot glass checkers then you should try satisfying your bottomless pit of a liver with this shot glass roulette drinking game!</brief>
<long>If somehow you are still sober after playing a couple of games of shot glass checkers then you should try satisfying your bottomless pit of a liver with this shot glass roulette drinking game! Makes a great gift for alcoholics and gamblers alike.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="7">
<title>Macintosh iPhone Case</title>
<url>http://schreerdelights.blogspot.com/2012/02/retro-iphone.html</url>
<description>
<price>$44.95</price>
<brief>Feel the nostalgia with this Macintosh iPhone case.</brief>
<long>Remember when Apple was the little guy? Now you can encase your trendy new iPhone with this nostalgic Macintosh case that reminds of you a simpler time in Apple history when they didn't dominate so many digital products. A must have collector's item for Mac lovers</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="8">
<title>Jeep Action Camper</title>
<url>http://www.actioncamper.info/details.php?artID=7</url>
<description>
<price>$53,000.00</price>
<brief>This jeep comes equipped with a camper</brief>
<long>Never before has living out of your car looked so appealing - the Jeep Action Camper is a slide on camper that provides an incredibly spacious and luxurious cabin with it's pop up roof. Perfect for outdoor camping, it amazing makes Jeeps even more versatile.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="9">
<title>The Water Jet Pack</title>
<url>http://www.jetlev-flyer.com/</url>
<description>
<price>$130,000.00</price>
<brief>The future has arrived...in a jet pack!</brief>
<long>Move over sliced bread, the <a href="http://youtu.be/im1iNq02Kz0" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Water Jet Pack</a> is officially the greatest thing ever. For only $130,000.00 you can own your very own water thrusting jetpack. The Water Jet Pack can lift you up over 20 feet high and thrust forward at 22 miles per hour.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="10">
<title>Camera Lens Coffee Mug</title>
<url>http://www.amazon.com/mn/search?field-keywords=camera%20coffee%20cup&#038;tag=051-20</url>
<description>
<price>$25.00</price>
<brief>You should think twice about using your own expensive lens like this.</brief>
<long>This high quality and super detailed camera lens is actually a coffee mug you can drink out of! The camera lens coffee mug is a great gift for photography enthusiasts, and will surely turn many heads when people see you drinking out of it.</long>
</description>
</item>
</products>
