<products>
<item id="1">
<title>Soap Bar Flakes Dispenser</title>
<url>http://www.nathaliestaempfli.com/index.php?/graduation/soap-flakes/</url>
<description>
<price>Concept</price>
<brief>Never drop the soap again with this soap shaver.</brief>
<long>Don't live in fear of dropping those slippy soap bars in the showers - now you can easily shave off little flakes from a bar of soap with this clever soap dispensing tool. Prisons every where are already reporting a drop in shower rapes thanks to this wonderful shaver.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="2">
<title>Sea Monster Ceiling Lamp</title>
<url>http://teptec.net/?page_id=728</url>
<description>
<price>$489.89</price>
<brief>Does your home need more Half Life barnacles lighting your house?</brief>
<long>Light up your home or bedroom in a horrifying manner with these sea monster ceiling lamps that are reminiscent of the attacking barnacles from Half-Life. These incredibly detailed custom made ceiling lamps are limited in quantity - though a "do-it-yourself" tutorial is planned.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="3">
<title>Glow Crowbar</title>
<url>http://glowbar.myshopify.com/products/glowbar-classic</url>
<description>
<price>$49.99</price>
<brief>A 2-in-1 tool for lighting and breaking in!</brief>
<long>Are you having trouble seeing at night while performing a breaking and entering? Could you use some added lighting while you beat someone in a dark alley? If you answered yes, then the glow in the dark crowbar is a the right tool for you!</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="4">
<title>Nintendo Guitar</title>
<url>http://www.w3shstore.com/miroir-de-poche-mirrorbook-air.html</url>
<description>
<price>$26.00</price>
<brief>What happens when you fuse a NES to a guitar?</brief>
<long>Classic Nintendo game systems don't die - they evolve! These <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vf4XN0L6LX0" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Nintendo guitars</a> are custom made fully functional six string guitars with all the working features you'd expect from a real guitar. Available in several wood styles, these electric Nintendo guitars are a must have item.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="5">
<title>Pillow Fight Weapons</title>
<url>http://www.bryanku.com/Pillow-Fight</url>
<description>
<price>Concept</price>
<brief>Pillow weapons are the best excuse for a pillow fight!</brief>
<long>Pillow fights aren't a kid's game anymore - pick up your battle axe and get ready for things to get ugly - the pillow wars have begun! These shaped pillows include a scimitar, grenade, nunchucks, ninja star, battle axe, and even a light saber pillow weapon!</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="6">
<title>Amplifier Fridge</title>
<url>http://marshallfridge.com/</url>
<description>
<price>$299.99</price>
<brief>What is rock and roll without beer?</brief>
<long>Beer and rock and roll have always gone together perfectly, but this signature Marshall amp fridge takes it to a whole new level. With control knobs that go all the way up to 11, this incredibly detailed amplifier fridge holds 4.4 cubic feet of food and drinks.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="7">
<title>Macintosh iPhone Case</title>
<url>http://schreerdelights.blogspot.com/2012/02/retro-iphone.html</url>
<description>
<price>$44.95</price>
<brief>Feel the nostalgia with this Macintosh iPhone case.</brief>
<long>Remember when Apple was the little guy? Now you can encase your trendy new iPhone with this nostalgic Macintosh case that reminds of you a simpler time in Apple history when they didn't dominate so many digital products. A must have collector's item for Mac lovers</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="8">
<title>Jeep Action Camper</title>
<url>http://www.actioncamper.info/details.php?artID=7</url>
<description>
<price>$53,000.00</price>
<brief>This jeep comes equipped with a camper</brief>
<long>Never before has living out of your car looked so appealing - the Jeep Action Camper is a slide on camper that provides an incredibly spacious and luxurious cabin with it's pop up roof. Perfect for outdoor camping, it amazing makes Jeeps even more versatile.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="9">
<title>The Water Jet Pack</title>
<url>http://www.jetlev-flyer.com/</url>
<description>
<price>$130,000.00</price>
<brief>The future has arrived...in a jet pack!</brief>
<long>Move over sliced bread, the <a href="http://youtu.be/im1iNq02Kz0" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Water Jet Pack</a> is officially the greatest thing ever. For only $130,000.00 you can own your very own water thrusting jetpack. The Water Jet Pack can lift you up over 20 feet high and thrust forward at 22 miles per hour.</long>
</description>
</item>
<item id="10">
<title>Camera Lens Coffee Mug</title>
<url>http://www.amazon.com/mn/search?field-keywords=camera%20coffee%20cup&#038;tag=051-20</url>
<description>
<price>$25.00</price>
<brief>You should think twice about using your own expensive lens like this.</brief>
<long>This high quality and super detailed camera lens is actually a coffee mug you can drink out of! The camera lens coffee mug is a great gift for photography enthusiasts, and will surely turn many heads when people see you drinking out of it.</long>
</description>
</item>
</products>
